乖狗狗
Good boy.
小心點  小心點
Watch it. Watch it.
弗蘭克  不要這樣
Frank, no.
早說了讓你別這樣做
Told you not to do that.
-給點零錢吧  -不好意思  夥計
- Spare any change? - Whoa! Uh, s- sorry, man.
我一塊錢都沒有  我
Uh, I don't have any money. I just...
那好吧
Yeah, right.
對不起  兄弟
Whoa. Sorry, bro.
長點眼  夥計
Watch it, man.
嘿  想一起抵制氣候變暖嗎
Hey, stop global warming?
不好意思  我不會說英語
So sorry. No speak English.
-好吧  -對不起
- Okay. - So sorry.
打擾一下  想聯名呼籲抵制氣候變暖嗎
Excuse me. Would you like to sign this to stop global warming?
別吹了
Shut up!
我在做噩夢
I'm having bad dreams
我睜眼躺著
I lie awake...
哦  你會永遠這樣的
Oh, you're taking forever!
她回來了嗎
She's back?
-出去  -我不要再去車裡面睡了
- Out. - I'm not sleeping in my car again.
-裡面聞起來就像屎一樣  -出去
- It smells like Hot Pockets and feet. - Get out.
我只是想來換個內褲
I just want clean underwear.
這也是我的房間啊
It's my room, too.
老天鵝啊  接電話  瑞恩
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
怎麼了
What?
瑞恩  老兄  我的天啊
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
快來找我  夥計  這太瘋狂了
Get over here right now, man. This is crazy.
我的天吶  你不會相信這事的
Oh, my God. You're not gonna believe this.
你傻嗎  我至少懂一點點吧
Fool, I understood two percent of that.
老兄  快過來吧
Dude, just come now!
哪裡
Where?
-老兄  老兄  -怎麼了
- Dude! Dude. - What?
你得馬上進來看看
You need to get in here right now. Huh?
-最好別是什麼壞事  -當然是好事
- This better be good, man. - It is.
房間161
量子
力學
1號實驗室
快點  快來
Come on, come on.
-哇哦  -沒騙你吧
- Whoa. - Right?
0.7米勒頓的能量
.7 millinewtons of energy.
天吶  這  這看起來可是大發現
God, that's... that's, like, huge.
-什麼時候發現的  -昨天12:01
- When? - Uh, yesterday. 12:01 A.M.
天吶  這也太瘋狂了  夥計
Damn, this is crazy, man.
沒錯瑞恩  但不知道是什麼觸發了設備
Yeah, but, Ryan, we have no idea what set the device off.
我是說  實驗室是鎖著的
Like, lab was locked.
就好像是設備自己運作了
It's almost like it decided to fire on its own.
就是這樣吧  我受夠了
That's it! I've had it!
哦  糟糕
Oh, shit.
嘿  你們要去哪裡
Hey. Wh... Where you guys going?
-餐廳有教堂日活動  -開吃嘍
- It's churro day at the cafeteria. - Nom, nom.
布洛森院長  你好啊
Dean Bronson, hi.
領帶不錯  上面那些是貓咪嗎
Love the tie. Uh, are those cats?
是土耳其安哥拉貓  不要轉移話題
Turkish angora. Uh, d- don't change the subject.
-什麼話題  -那個
- What subject? - That.
我們有4個設備突然斷電
We've had four rolling blackouts,
電路都被燒壞了
fried electrical circuits,
還燒壞了學校所有的燈泡
broken bulbs all over campus.
而這一切都歸功於你的小實驗
And it's all because of your little science project.
-這是我論文的項目  -是必然的失敗
- It's my thesis project. - It's an abject failure.
我們大學的科學部門
This university's science department
因開拓超前思維並能產生成果而自豪
prides itself on pioneering forward-thinking ideas that yield results.
最後將成果轉化為專利權
Results that lead to patents.
你看不出這其中的緣由嗎
Do you see how it works?
就是為了錢嗎
So, it's just about money?
沒錯  凡先生
Yes, Mr. Phan.
我並不想粉碎你的幻想
I hate to shatter your illusions,
但是總得有人打開天窗說亮話
but somebody has to keep the lights on around here,
你的實驗項目必須馬上停止
something you seem hell-bent on stopping!
徹底停止  就當這項目被懸停了吧
Literally! Consider this joke of a project suspended,
停止指令立即生效
effective immediately.
-什麼  -就是這樣
- What? - That's right.
我已經給伯納教授打了電話
I've already called Professor Boner.
是邦納
It's pronounced "Bonner."
他完全贊同我的要求
And he's in total agreement with my request.
我已經讓保安人員今天6點鐘來收走
I'm sending security to come and collect
你這吸收能量的破玩意兒
this energy-sucking doohickey by 6:00 today.
你不能就這樣把它帶走
You can't just take her.
好好聽我說  我建議你盡快打包帶走
Watch me. I suggest you wrap up
你留在這裡的東西  收到了嗎
whatever business you have left here, capisce?
有人嗎
Hello?
搞什麼鬼
What the hell?
止步
限制區域
僅相關人員可入內
房間156
2號實驗室
嘿  噁心的傢伙
Hey, shit bags.
你在玩偷拍小遊戲的同時
While you were off playing games,
我的實驗項目被勒令停止了
our project got shut down.
這下你開心了嗎
I hope you're happy.
你發什麼神經
What is wrong with you?
-幹嘛偷偷摸摸過來  -我給你帶了個
- Why are you sneaking up on me? - I was bringing you a...
這下好了  沾滿細菌了
Well, now it's covered in bacteria,
兩美元就這麼浪費掉了
so that's two dollars wasted.
太無情了
So ungrateful.
乖狗狗
Good boy.
弗蘭克  不要這樣
Frank, no.
小伙子  你什麼毛病
Dude, what's your problem?
對不起  夥計  我
I'm so sorry, man. I...
真的對不起
So sorry.
混球
Dick.
不好意思  兄弟
Sorry, bro.
別吹了
Shut up!
我在做噩夢
I'm having bad dreams
我睜眼躺著
I lie awake...
哦  你會永遠這樣的
Oh, you're taking forever!
出去
Out.
瑞恩
Ryan.
老兄  我現在應該是在夢遊
Dude, I am tripping right now.
是的  沒錯
Yeah, no shit.
不  不  不  我說認真的
No. No, no, seriously.
我有那種能力  你知道嗎
I'm having that thing. You know?
該怎麼說呢  就像是感覺已經
What's it called? When you feel like you've already
經歷過現在發生的一切
lived through something before.
-昨日重來的感覺嗎  -就是這個感覺
- Deja vu? - Yes, that.
感覺我從頭到尾經歷過今天這一切了
I feel like I've totally lived through this day already.
老天鵝啊  接電話  瑞恩
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
瑞恩  老兄  我的天啊
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
快來找我  夥計
Get over here right now, man.
這太瘋狂了  我的天吶
This is crazy. Oh, my God.
我  我等會兒打給你
I- I got to call you back.
好的  深呼吸
Okay. Just breathe.
呼吸
Just breathe.
聽我說
Listen to me.
你死那天的經歷又重來了一遍  對嗎
The day reset when you died, right?
是的  有個瘋子戴著嬰兒面具攻擊了我
Yeah. Some psycho dude in a baby mask attacked me.
但那只是一個夢  對嗎
But it was just a dream, right?
-湯布斯死了  -羅麗也是
- Tombs is dead. - So is Lori.
那這次誰是兇手
Then who's the killer this time?
能聽我說嗎
Uh, hello.
你們誰能告訴我這他媽的到底是怎麼了
Will someone please explain what the hell is going on?
好吧  再說一遍
Okay. Recap.
我在不停地重複經歷同一天
So, I was stuck reliving the same day,
18號  星期一  一遍又一遍地經歷
Monday the 18th, over and over and over again
直到一個戴著詭異娃娃臉面具的人
until someone wearing a Bayfield Baby mask
在我生日那天晚上殺了我
murdered me on the night of my birthday.
我起初完全不知道那是誰
I had no idea who it was
因為我是點婊
because I was such a crazy bitch
有太多的人對我恨之入骨
and so many people hated my guts.
在卡特的建議下  我列了個嫌疑人名單
So, at Carter's suggestion, I made a list of suspects.
最後發現兇手原來是我室友  羅麗
Turns out it was my roommate, Lori,
她一直在幫一個連環殺手逃出醫院
who kept on helping a serial killer escape from the hospital,
希望看起來像是那個殺手殺了我
hoping it would look like he murdered me when,
但實際上一直都是她
in fact, it was her all along,
而這一切就因為她嫉妒我和
and all because she was jealous of an affair I was having
大學已婚的格瑞格裡教授有一腿
with my college professor, Gregory, who was married.
是的  我知道這太不要臉了
Yeah, I know. Pretty shitty.
但是  無論如何
But, anyways,
我最終還是將羅麗踢出窗外  殺死了她
I finally kicked Lori's crazy ass out a window and killed her,
從而終止了時間循環  我是這麼想的
which broke the loop, or so I thought.
但現在看起來  時間循環傳到了你這裡
But now it only looks like it passed the loop on to you
而你將會不停的重複這一切
and you're gonna be stuck reliving this day
直到我們想出辦法
until we figure out how to stop it.
當然了
Of course.
我還在做夢吧
I'm still dreaming.
等等  你說什麼
Wait. What?
這就像《盜夢空間》
It's like Inception.
夢中還有夢
It's a dream within a dream.
老兄  你可不是在做夢
Bro, you're not dreaming.
-瑞恩  我們  -噓
- Ryan, we... - Shh.
我在試著讓自己醒過來
I'm trying to wake myself up.
看見沒  這不是夢境
There. See? You're not dreaming.
你為什麼打我的雞雞
Why'd you hit my penis?
你怎麼反應這麼大
Why are you acting like this?
你打了我的雞雞  這太粗魯了
You smacked my dick. That's rude.
我都沒碰到你
I barely touched you.
好吧  告訴我你在哪裡死的
Okay. Show me where you died.
在那後面  儲物櫃那裡
Back there. Storage closet.
嘿  把棒球棍給我
Hey. Give me that.
我自己能行
I can handle myself.
你還沒死夠嗎
You've died enough, haven't you?
-給他致命一擊  -噓
- Bash his head in. - Shh! - Shh!
我丟你老母的
-薩瑪  你個混球  -你為什麼打我
- Samar, you asshole! - Why'd you hit me?
你為什麼在我後面偷偷摸摸的
Why do you keep sneaking up on me?
我覺得我顴骨斷了
Ah, I think my cheekbone's broken.
這裡發生了什麼
What is happening in here?
瑞恩打斷了我的顴骨
Ryan broke my cheekbone.
-兇手是他嗎  -不是
- Was it him? - No.
上次我死的時候他就在我眼前
He was here when I died before.
什麼
What?
你從哪裡拿到的面具
Where'd you get that mask?
它就在樓道裡啊
It was just laying in the hallway.
不知道誰扔在那裡的
Somebody must have dropped it.
就這樣吧  我受夠了
That's it. I've had it.
等等  你們去哪裡
Wait, wait. Where you going?
-餐廳有教堂日活動  -開吃嘍
- Uh, churro day at the cafeteria. - Nom, nom.
我們有4個設備突然斷電
We've had four rolling blackouts,
電路都被燒壞了
fried electrical circuits,
還燒壞了學校所有的燈泡
broken bulbs all over campus.
而這一切都歸功於你的小實驗
And it's all because of your little science project.
等等
Wait.
什麼小實驗
What science project?
西西弗斯量子冷卻反應堆
The Sisyphus Quantum Cooling Reactor.
我們簡稱西西裝置
We call it Sissy for short.
看到這些了嗎
You see all these?
這是質子發射器
They're proton lasers.
設備被激活的時候  會冷卻那個離心機
And when they fire, they cool the centrifuge right here
熱量接近到10的負9次方開爾文
to almost below one nanokelvin.
可以說  我們正試著證明時間
So, basically, we're trying to prove that time
可以在分子級別被減速
can be slowed down on a molecular level.
現在雖然還沒有見效
It hasn't worked yet,
但就在一個晚上這個設備被激活的時候
but we did find some promising data
我們發現了一些有力的數據
after the device fired the other night.
什麼時候
When?
昨天早上12:01
12:01 A.M. yesterday.
18號  星期一那天
Monday the 18th.
怎麼了
What?
你創造了這個時間循環  白癡
You created the time loop, dummy.
這不可能
That's impossible.
這可不是設計西西裝置的設計初衷啊
That's not what Sissy was designed to do.
我不知道該說什麼
I don't know what to tell you.
也許我們剛好發現了
Well, maybe we're just discovering
它真正的功能
what it actually does.
一個猝不及防的結果
An unintended reaction.
也許我們認為可以將時間減速
Maybe we thought we were slowing time,
但實際上我們讓它循環了
but what if we looped it instead?
所以說你卡在今天了
Now you're stuck in this day.
祝賀你
Congrats.
順便提醒你  你會死
Oh, and by the way, you're gonna die
一遍又一遍地死
again and again and again.
卡特  告訴你女朋友不要再來嚇我了
Carter, tell your girlfriend to stop trying to scare me.
她不算我女朋友
Oh, she's not my girlfriend.
-等等  你是我女朋友嗎  -算是吧
- Well, wait, are you my girlfriend? - Kinda.
嘿  夥計們
Hey, guys,
能暫時放下你們之間的關係問題嗎
are you done talking about your relationship status?
因為她剛剛說了我會死
Because she just said I'm gonna die.
而你得盡快找辦法去停止時間循環
And you need to figure out how to close the loop
不然那個殺手會再次殺了你
before the killer finds you again.
但我不知道發生了什麼啊
But I don't know how it happened.
那個設備就自己運行了
It just fired on its own.
我的天
Oh, God.
丹妮爾  你好啊
Danielle. Hi.
-你去哪裡了  -什麼意思
- Where were you? - What do you mean?
你沒參加我們的寢室會
You ditched our house meeting.
-不是取消了嗎  -什麼時候的事
- It was canceled. - When?
在我把殺人的室友踢出窗外之後
Um, after I kicked my murdering roommate out of a window.
沒錯  是誰天天向卡帕祈禱
Exactly. Who's gonna pledge Kappa
說我們中了死亡詛咒
now that we have a death curse?
還說我們現在很危險  翠
We're in crisis mode, Tree.
這些都是什麼人
Who are these people?
你好
Hi.
呃  我是  我是薩瑪
Uh, I'm- I'm- I'm Samar.
嘿  薩莫薩  眼睛看哪裡呢
Hey, Samosa, my head's the middle one.
薩莫薩是一種三角炸餃, 南亞食品
不管怎樣  在你們的詭異會談弄完之後
Anyhoo, call me as soon as you're done
盡快給我打電話
with your creepy little Comic-Con meeting. Ugh.
她剛剛叫我"薩莫薩"嗎
Did she just call me "samosa"?
是的
Yep.
-你覺得她喜歡薩莫薩嗎  -不喜歡
- You think she likes samosas? - Nope.
夥計們  別分心  我還不想死
Guys, focus. I don't want to die.
樂觀點來說  你會復活的
On the bright side, you'll come back.
我死了11次
I died 11 times.
11次嗎  他奶奶的
11? Hell no.
-被殺很疼的  -等等
- That shit hurts. - Wait a minute.
夥計們  我有個主意
Guys, I have an idea.
我們只要找個最安全的地方
We just need to find the safest possible place
然後在那裡等殺手不就行了嗎
and wait it out there.
哪裡呢
Where?
怎麼了
What?
人山人海的地方不就挺安全的嗎
There's... safety in numbers.
還不如說是躲在眾目睽睽之下
More like hiding in plain sight.
哪個鬼才選的詭異娃娃臉面具來當吉祥物
Who picks a creepy baby for a mascot anyway?
早知道就去麻省理工了
I knew I should have gone to M.I.T.
他走步違規了吧
He traveled!
三不沾嘍
Airball!
那是你和你媽媽嗎
Is that you and your mom?
太有愛了
That's cute.
我在想
I was thinking.
這太諷刺了
It's ironic.
我想  因為某些莫名其妙的原因
Here I thought I was stuck in the same day
我困在同一天了
for some big cosmic reason.
你知道嗎  面對媽媽的死亡
You know, facing my mom's death.
卻無能為力
It had nothing to do with her.
結果卻發現這只是一個科學的意外
Turns out it was just some big scientific fluke.
但這並沒有失去它的意義  不是嗎
That doesn't make it mean any less, does it?
是吧
I guess not.
你那裡沾了點東西
Oh, you got a little something right here.
好了
Yep, uh, uh.
是嗎
Yeah.
對不起  這
Sorry. It's...
你這太老套了
You're such a grandpa.
是啊  但你還是上當了
Yeah, well, you fell for it, so...
請大家從最近的出口離開
Please make your way to the nearest exit
保持好秩序
in an orderly fashion.
這不是演習
This is not a drill.
請大家從最近的出口離開
Please make your way to the nearest exit
保持好秩序
in an orderly fashion.
重複  這不是演習
Again, this is not a drill.
嘿  小心點
Hey, watch it!
夥計們  等等我
Guys! Wait up!
別推我
Don't push me.
嘿  我找不到手機了
Hey, I can't find my phone.
救我  幫幫我  求求你們
Help! Help! Please!
救救我
Help!
-什麼人  -來下面
- What was that? - Down here!
見鬼
Holy shit.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
應該沒問題
Yeah, I think so.
厲害啊  做的不錯
Well, damn. Good job.
-我之前可是練過的  -搞什麼呢
- I have a little practice. - What the hell?
我還以為你是兇手
I thought you were the killer.
你該出聲說句話的
You should have said something.
我剛剛在找你
I was looking for you.
那  這是誰
Well, who is it?
只有一個辦法能知道了
Only one way to find out.
什麼鬼
What the fu...?
你確定你  你沒有雙胞胎兄弟嗎
You sure you... you don't have a twin brother?
也許你們出生的時候就被分開了
Maybe you were separated at birth.
當然  我很確定
Of course I'm sure.
-見鬼  -確實是"見鬼"了
- Oh, shit. - "Oh, shit" is right.
你是誰
Who are you?
你覺得我是誰  呆子
Who you think I am, dummy?
就是你
It's you.
-廢話  -廢話
- Duh. - Duh.
這到底是什麼情況
What the hell is going on here?
聽著  我在試圖關閉時間循環
Look, I was trying to close the loop,
但是我莫名其妙地進入了平行時間循環
but somehow I got knocked into a parallel time loop.
我們現在都非常危險
We're all in serious danger.
我們在同一空間出現的時間越長
The longer we exist in the same dimension,
就會發生越糟糕的事情
the worse things will get.
就像是蝴蝶效應
It's a butterfly effect.
你必須殺了他
You have to kill him.
-殺了我嗎  -如果你們不阻止他
- Me? - He's going to create bigger problems
他會給大家帶來更大的麻煩
if you do not stop him.
殺了他
Kill him now!
不  去他媽的  殺了他
No, screw that. Kill him.
你們是在浪費時間  快動手
You're wasting your time. Do it.
老兄  我才是你的朋友  他不是
Dude, I'm your friend, not him.
算了吧  去他媽的
Uh... you know what? Screw this.
我自己來處理我自己吧
I'll just take care of it myself.
-阻止他啊  -瑞恩  也許你該住手
- Stop him. - Wait. Ryan, maybe you should stop.
看看他  是他瘋了
Look at him. He's crazy.
我設計了這東西  我知道自己在幹什麼
I'm the one who designed this. I know what I'm doing.
你不明白你在做什麼
You don't understand what you're doing!
閉嘴  假瑞恩
Shut up, fake Ryan!
瑞恩  這感覺可不太對
Ryan, this doesn't feel right.
瑞恩  住手
Ryan, stop.
但是秒差距是距離單位  不是時間單位
But a parsec is a measure of distance, not time.
好吧  你覺得漢索羅是個騙子嗎
Okay, so now you're gonna call Han Solo a liar?
不  我是說如果凱瑟爾競賽說的是
No, I'm saying if a normal Kessel Run is...
隹  救我
Dre, help me.
快點
Come on!
老兄  你又給我飲料下藥了嗎
Dude, did you dose my Yoo-hoo again?
我是怎麼跟你說的  不要打開那個東西
What did I tell you about turning that thing on?
快把它關掉  現在立刻馬上
Turn it off now. Turn it off now!
抓住他  抓住那個人
Just get him. Get him. Get the man.
抓住他  抓住他啊
Get him, get him, get him!
退後  讓開
Back off! Back...
瑞恩  你就把它關掉吧
Ryan, just turn it off, man.
瑞恩  你在幹嘛啊
Ryan, what are you doing?
夥計們  把他手裡的扳手給我拿走
Guys, take the wrench from him.
連個學生都搞不定嗎
He's a college student.
只是個扳手
It's just a wrench.
別被他嚇到了
Don't be scared of him.
好的  好吧  拔掉電源的插頭
Okay, all right, just unplug it.
斷開電源  拔插頭
Unplug the machine. Unplug it!
系統充能中
不
No!
充能完畢
別吹了
Shut up!
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太確定你是否想多睡會兒
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not,
-所以我  -□耶  今天是我的生日
- so I... -□ Yeah, it's my birthday
-□我才不打算接電  -翠
-□ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho... - Tree?
他媽的別這樣
No fucking way.
我幫你疊好了衣服
Hey, I... I folded your clothes for you.
瑞恩  給我滾進來
Ryan! Get in here right now!
等等  你們互相認識嗎
Wait a minute, you two know each other?
-認識 -不認識
- Yes. - No.
瑞恩  你這個混球
Ryan, you dumbass!
你把我送回來了
You sent me back.
-什麼  -今天是18號  星期一
- What? - It's Monday the 18th.
我簡直不敢相信
I don't believe this.
我本來跳出了循環  你怎麼能這麼對我
I just got out. How could you do this to me?
這個神經女是誰
Uh... who's this crazy white girl?
也許這只是個噩夢什麼的
Maybe it was a-a bad dream or something.
你說的對  是個噩夢
You're right. It is a bad dream.
是個夢魘
It's a nightmare!
這太糟糕了
This sucks!
這簡直太扯淡了
It sucks the biggest mega balls
簡直是霉到家了
in the history of shitty ball-suckery!
這
It...
我沒事
I'm okay.
你確定嗎
You sure?
確定
Yes.
只是他必須彌補這一切
He just needs to fix this.
就現在
Now.
你們在開玩笑  對嗎
This is a joke, right?
我希望是開玩笑
I wish.
聽著
Look.
瑞恩  我們得去你的實驗室
Ryan, we need to go to your lab,
打開西西裝置
turn on Sissy,
然後想辦法把我送回去
and figure out how to send me back.
你是怎麼知道西西裝置的
Uh, how do you know about Sissy?
我的天  別管那麼多
Oh, my God. Just...
快走
Let's go.
跟上來啊  傻子們
Andale, people!
嘿  想一起抵制氣候變暖嗎
Hey. Stop global warming?
說一句"不了  謝謝"不行嗎
A simple "no, thanks" would do!
對不起
Sorry!
這他媽的就是同一天  同一天
This is the same day, same day,
同一天  同一天  又是同一天
same day, same day, same day!
□牆上有62個啤酒罐
□ 62 bottles of beer on the wall
我聽不見你說什麼
I can't hear you!
□62個啤酒罐
□ 62 bottles of beer
□你摘下一個  傳一圈
□ You take one down, pass it around
-繼續  -□牆上有61個啤酒罐
- Keep going! -□ 61 bottles of beer on the wall...
嘿  你還沒回我
Hey, you haven't returned any of...
你是個基佬
You are gay.
等等  你要去哪裡
Wait, where are you going?
實驗室要走這邊
The lab's back that way.
我有點事要先處理一下
I have some business to take care of first.
鬼鬼祟祟的小婊砸
You sneaky little beyatch.
怪了
That's weird.
什麼
What?
她本該在這裡的
She was supposed to be here.
誰
Who?
呃  沒什麼
Uh, never mind.
可算回來了
She finally rolls in.
它在哪裡
Where is it?
什麼在哪裡
Where's what?
-你好  卡特  -你好
- Oh, hey, Carter. - Hey.
紙杯蛋糕在哪裡
Where's the cupcake?
什麼紙杯蛋糕
What cupcake?
你為我生日做的那個
The one you made for my birthday.
你下毒了的那個
The one you poisoned.
那個紙杯蛋糕啊
Oh, that cupcake.
我認真的
I'm serious.
聽著  我不知道丹妮爾跟你開了
Look, I don't know what stupid joke
什麼愚蠢的玩笑  但沒有什麼紙杯蛋糕
Danielle put you up to, but there's no cupcake.
抱歉
Sorry.
好了  我得走了  我要替珍上班去了
All right, I got to go. I'm pulling a double for Jen.
她得流感了
She's got the flu.
不過還是  祝你生日快樂
Happy birthday, though.
拜拜
Toodles.
不太對勁
Something's wrong.
怎麼了
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
跟之前不一樣了
It's different.
-有兩個我嗎  -對
- There were two of me? - Yes.
整件事就因此而起
That is how this whole thing happened.
知道嗎  這讓我想起了《回到未來2》
You know, this kind of reminds me of Back to the Future II.
-沒錯  -對吧
- Totally. - Right?
-馬迪·麥克弗萊出演的  -還有博士
- You know, with Marty McFly? - Doc?
-迪羅倫呢  -聽不懂
- The DeLorean? - Sorry.
你認真的嗎  你沒看過《回到未來》嗎
Are you serious? You've never seen Back to the Future?
沒有  我
No, I...
-你是怎麼  -等等
- How do you... - Wait.
天啊
Oh, my God.
這是不是意味著
Does this mean that...
這是不是意味著會有兩個我
Does this mean that there are two of me?
我對此高度懷疑
I highly doubt it.
要創造一個全息宇宙幾乎是不可能的
It's almost impossible to create a holographic universe.
你可能是被困在一個量子循環維度裡了
You're probably stuck in a quantum cyclic dimension.
這個維度裡只有一個你
There's only one of you here,
因為另一個你被撞進
because the other you got knocked into
一個多元宇宙裡的某個平行維度去了
a parallel dimension somewhere in the multiverse.
好的  瑞恩  謝謝你的解釋
Okay, Ryan. Thanks for clearing that up.
真是太有用了呢
That was super helpful.
你從沒聽過多元宇宙論嗎
You never heard the multiverse theory?
我看起來像是知道多元宇宙是什麼的人嗎
Do I look like someone who knows what a multiverse is?
好吧  聽著  這是我們的宇宙
Okay, look. This is our universe.
明白嗎  好好看著
Okay? Now, look.
理論上  宇宙有六個維度
In theory, the universe has six dimensions.
那麼  如果你說的是真的
Now, if what you're saying is true,
也許你在同一天醒來
then maybe you woke up on the same day...
卻不在同一個維度裡
but not in the same dimension.
這就可以解釋那些異常現象了
That would explain the anomalies.
所以  有多異常呢
So, how different are we talking here?
那就看情況了
Well, it depends.
糟糕  我把寢室會給忘了
Oh, shit. I forgot our house meeting.
丹妮爾  抱歉  我只是
Danielle, I'm sorry. I just...
嘿  寶貝
Hey, babe.
你好嗎
You doing all right?
你好  瑞
Hi, Ry.
你好  丹妮爾
Hey, Danielle.
我演的像嗎
Did that look real?
我正在為今年的
I'm auditioning for this year's production
《奇跡締造者》的試鏡做準備
of The Miracle Worker.
你知道安妮·弗蘭克又聾又瞎嗎
Did you know Anne Frank was blind and deaf?
是海倫·凱勒
Uh... Helen Keller.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
安妮·弗蘭克是那個在閣樓的女孩
Anne Frank was in the attic.
這樣啊
Oh.
管他呢
Whatever.
我只知道裝瞎就行了
All I know is acting blind
可能比真瞎還要難
is probably harder than actually being blind.
我是說  它需要演技
I mean, the skill set it takes.
梅麗爾·斯特裡普為了準備這個角色
Meryl Streep taped her eyelids shut
把她的眼皮都粘住了
just to prepare for a role.
對了  今天有人錯過了我們的寢室會
Well. Somebody missed our house meeting today.
我很抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I...
我開玩笑的
Totes kidding.
小壽星有豁免權
Birthday girls get a free pass.
話說回來  我們選定了今年的慈善主題
Anyhoo, we picked this year's charity.
我要宣佈了哦
Are you ready for it?
我們要再辦一次募捐藝術展
We're doing the special needs art fair again.
真棒
Oh. Nice.
你這可是大善舉  丹妮爾
You do so much good, Danielle.
我很佩服你
I-I really admire that.
拜託別這樣  看到那些小臉兒
Oh, please. It just warms my heart
我的心都要化了
seeing all those little faces.
我是說  你們別理解錯了
I mean, don't get me wrong.
有時候他們抱著你久久不放
Sometimes they try to hug you too long,
確實有點讓人不舒服
and it gets a little uncomfortable,
但習慣就好了
but you just get used to it.
說到底
And at the end of the day,
人生中沒有什麼饋贈
there is no greater gift in life
能比孩子們的愛再珍貴的了
than the love of a child.
謝謝你
Thank you.
翠
Tree?
你還好嗎
You okay?
呃  我沒事  我
Uh... yeah, I...
□耶  今天是我的生日
□ Yeah, it's my birthday
-□我才不打算接電話  -抱歉
- □And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. - Sorry.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, Dad. Um...
呃  對  對
Uh... Yeah, yeah.
抱歉  我這就來
Sorry. I'm on my way.
我馬上就到
I'll be there in a little bit.
我得走了
I have to go. Um...
等一下  什麼  你要走了嗎
Wait, what? You're leaving?
對  我得去和我爸爸吃午飯
Uh, yeah. I have to meet up with my dad for lunch.
生日慣例
It's a birthday thing.
三點鐘在實驗室見
Meet me in the lab at 3:00.
在事情變得更糟糕前  趕緊想點辦法
We are figuring this out before it gets any worse!
-嘿  爸爸  -嘿
- Hey, Dad. - Hey.
-抱歉我來晚了  -沒事的 寶貝
- Sorry I'm late. - It's okay, sweetie.
一整天都怪怪的
It's just been a weird day.
-一切都好嗎  -還好
- Everything okay? - Uh, yeah.
每天也都那樣  你知道的
It's just... stuff, you know.
在學校過的怎麼樣
How's school?
還好吧  爸爸
Um, it's fine, Dad.
-可以點餐了嗎  -稍等
- Are you ready to order? - Not yet.
我們還要等一個人
We're still waiting on one more.
還有一個人嗎  我
One more? I...
好的  那我稍後再來
Okay. I'll be right back.
媽媽
Mom.
Mom!
你好
Hi.
你來了
You're here.
你真的來了
Oh, you're really here.
我當然要來  今天可是我們的大日子
Well, of course I'm here. It's our day.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
好  當然好
Yeah. Yeah.
天啊  我沒事  我只是
Oh, God, I'm fine. I'm just...
見到你真好
It's good to see you.
好了
Okay.
現在試試吧
Try it now.
20秒
20 seconds.
發生這些算正常嗎
Yo, is this normal?
別擔心  不會再爆炸了
Don't worry, it's not gonna blow up again.
-你說"再"嗎  -十  九
- Again? - Ten. Nine.
八  七
Eight. Seven.
六  五
Six. Five.
四  三
Four. Three.
二
Two.
停下
Stop!
快停下
Leave it.
-是你讓我  -我知道
- You told me to... - No, I-I know.
我改變主意了
I changed my mind.
這一定就是那個神經女了
This must be the crazy white girl.
嘿  翠  等一下
Hey, Tree. Wait up.
嘿  等下
Hey. Hey.
你怎麼改變主意了
Why the change of heart?
-一切都不一樣了  -什麼不一樣了
- Everything's different. - Different how?
等等  你打算什麼時候告訴我
Wait, when were you gonna tell me?
告訴你什麼
Tell you what?
丹妮爾的事
About Danielle.
丹妮爾怎麼了
Yeah, what about Danielle?
顯然你們兩個在一起了
Apparently you guys are dating.
等等  我以為  我以為你知道的
Wait, I thought... I thought you knew that.
我是說  你們住在一起
I mean, you guys live in the same house.
不知道  我絕對不知道
Uh, no, I definitely didn't know.
但最大的問題是  她知道嗎
But the bigger question is: does she know?
她知道什麼
Does she know what?
她最好的朋友之一早上是在你床上醒來的
One of her closest friends woke up in your bed this morning.
你不覺得應該告訴她嗎
You don't think that that's newsworthy?
什麼都沒發生啊
Nothing happened.
我昨晚睡的是瑞恩的床
I slept in Ryan's bed last night.
所以  為什麼帶我回家呢
So, why take me home?
因為你  因為你醉倒了
Because you were... you were wasted.
我怕你摔倒
I was afraid you were gonna fall
或者跟詹尼斯·喬普林一樣被嘔吐物嗆到
or choke on your own vomit like Janis Joplin.
好吧
Okay.
沒關係  沒事的
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
沒關係  本來就應該這樣
It's fine. This is how it's supposed to be.
我媽媽沒事  羅麗沒有想殺我
My mom's okay. Lori isn't trying to kill me.
這個版本的人生更好
I mean, this is, like, the better version
-不是嗎  -你在
- of my life, right? - What are you...?
她在聯誼會裡  格瑞格裡  她
She's in a sorority, Gregory. She's...
等一下  難道
Wait a minute. In this...
在這個維度裡  我們
in this other dimension, were we...?
我先不跟你說了
I... I can't do this right now.
別這樣  翠
No, Tr... Tree!
你準備好了嗎
Are you ready for this?
好了  拿著這個
I... No. Okay. Hold this.
然後
And...
我的天
Oh, my God!
太奇怪了
It's so weird.
太好吃了
Oh, my... this is amazing.
但我覺得你不能再吃了
But I don't think you have to get another one.
這是我吃過最棒的
This is, like, the best...
這些記憶沒有一個是屬於我的
None of these memories are mine.
我知道這是你的  我就今晚借一下
I know. I'm just borrowing it for tonight.
你什麼時候去派對呢
What time you going to the party?
我  我不能去了
Um... I, uh... I can't make it.
-出了一些事情  -什麼情況
- Something came up. - What?
我是說
I mean,
我們已經為這個準備好幾周了  翠
we've been planning this for weeks, Tree.
我知道  我知道這是一個驚喜派對
No, I know. And I know it's a surprise party.
我很抱歉  只是
I'm sorry. It's just...
我的父母來城裡了  我需要
You know, my parents are in town, and I need to...
我們交的學費也該起作用了
Ugh. Our tuition dollars at work.
總之  誰告訴你有一個驚喜派對的
Anyhoo, who told you about the surprise?
是羅麗嗎
Was it Lori?
我發誓  那個女孩
I swear, that girl
真的需要學會如何保守秘密
really needs to learn how to keep a secret.
我不知道你是怎麼了
I don't know what's going on with you...
你知道嗎  翠  我就跟你直說吧
You know what, Tree, I'm just gonna come out and say it.
我感覺特別的
I have been feeling so extremely
-不被你欣賞  -報道一則槍擊案
- unappreciated by you... - ...following a deadly shootout
發生於今早導致一名警員死亡
this morning that left one officer dead.
你在聽嗎
Hello?
我在跟你說話呢
I'm still talking to you.
湯布斯正在被全國追捕
Tombs was the subject of a nationwide manhunt
他在五個月裡橫跨四個州
that ended after a five-month pursuit across four state lines
殺害了六名女性
that left six female victims.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他還在這裡
He's still here.
他要逃跑了  趕緊報警
He's going to escape! Call the police!
誰要跑了
Who?
約翰·湯布斯  趕緊報警
John Tombs. Just call the police.
-什麼情況  -等一下  別進去
- What? - Wait! Don't go in there!
該死
Shit.
你等下  你在做什麼
Excuse me. What are you doing?
放下斧子
Whoa. Drop the ax.
-等等  我可以解  -馬上放下斧子
- Wait. I can expl... - Drop it now.
他已經逃跑了  他要殺人了
He's escaped. He's gonna kill someone.
-面對牆站好  -你不明白  羅麗要
- Face up against the wall. - No, you don't understand. Lori...
我不會問第二遍
I'm not asking again.
請你聽我解釋
Please listen to me.
我的舍友在這裡工作
My roommate works here.
她放走了湯布斯因為她想要陷害他
She set Tombs free because she's trying to blame him,
但是她要殺了我
but she's gonna kill me.
我不知道你嗑了什麼藥  女士
I don't know what kind of shit you're on, lady,
但是湯布斯現在正在手術室裡
but Tombs is down in the O.R. right now.
護士剛剛帶走他
Nurse just took him.
那護士是不是很高  深黑頭髮梳著馬尾
Was she tall, dark hair and a ponytail?
我們走吧
Let's go.
我知道你覺得我瘋了  但是你得相信我
I know you think I'm crazy, but you got to believe me.
派遣中心  我是康羅警官
Dispatch, this is Officer Conrow.
醫院裡有人襲警
Have an 11-55 at the hospital.
需要緊急支援
Need immediate assistance.
快點啊
Come on.
我知道是你  羅麗
I know it's you, Lori!
-什麼情況  -我的天啊
- What? - Oh, my God!
我的天啊  我以為你是
Oh, my God. I thought you were the...
你沒事吧  這他媽的發生什麼了
Are you okay? What the hell is going on?
-那是誰  -湯布斯逃走了
- Who was that? - Tombs escaped.
他想殺了我
He's trying to kill me.
不可能  那是不可能的  翠
No, Tree, that's not possible.
我剛剛把他推到手術室去
I just took him down to the O.R.
發生什麼了
What's happening?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
我的天啊  他把電斷了
Oh, my God, he cut the power.
保持冷靜
Just stay calm.
保持冷靜  該死
Just stay calm. Shit!
好吧  把門拉開吧
Okay. Come on.
過來吧
Come on.
我們這是在哪
Where the hell are we?
這裡肯定是待建樓層
This must be one of the floors under construction.
快點  在另一頭肯定有緊急出口
Come on. There's an emergency exit on the other end.
等一下
Wait.
把那個拿上
Grab that.
好的
Okay.
怎麼了
What?
你聽到什麼了嗎
Did you hear something?
好吧  混蛋  讓我看看你有什麼能耐
All right, asshole, let's see what you got.
該死
Shit!
別吹了
Shut up!
太菜了  翠
Rookie move, Tree.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我在哪一個維度
What dimension am I in?
丹妮爾
Danielle.
我女朋友嗎
Uh, my girlfriend?
還是那個維度
Same one.
-□耶  今天是我的生日
-□ Yeah, it's my birthday
□我才不打算接電話
□ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho...
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
沒事
Yeah.
好的不能再好了
Never better.
我幫你疊好了衣服  所以
Hey, I folded your clothes for you, so...
聽著  無意冒犯
Look, no offense,
但是你怎麼可能和她在一起呢
but how could you possibly end up with her?
和誰啊
With who?
丹妮爾
Danielle.
因為  她很好相處
Uh, uh, she's nice.
好吧  "好相處"
Oh, "nice."
等一下
Wait a minute.
她難道不是  你最好的朋友嗎
Isn't she, like, your best friend?
老兄  你是把那妞上了嗎還是怎
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or wha...?
-這真有趣  -沒有  我沒做過任何
-Huh. Interesting. - No, I wasn't trying to do any...
-你不如你看起來那麼單純哦  -但是
- Not as innocent as you look. - But...
-什麼  我  -你
- What? No, I-I... - You.
一小時後在你的實驗室見
Meet me in your lab in an hour.
我不想再穿這些噁心的衣服了
I've got to get out of these disgusting clothes.
仔細聽我說
Listen to me carefully.
我需要留在這個維度裡
I need to stay here in this dimension.
明白嗎  所以把時間循環關掉吧
Okay? So just close the loop.
聽著  我們完全不知道
Look, we have no idea
這件事情一開始是怎麼發生的
how this even happened in the first place.
你們不都是聰明的科學人士嗎
Well, you're all brainy science people, right?
所以你們會弄明白的
So you'll figure it out.
你明白我們在折騰
You realize we're messing
一些我們從未接觸過的事情  對嗎
with things we have no business touching, right?
在你們開始搭建那巨大的蠢東西之前
Well, maybe you should have thought of that
你們就應該想到這一點
before you built the big dumb thing.
拜託  拜託幫我一個忙
Just... just please do me a favor
想想辦法弄明白這個  好嗎
and try to figure this out, okay?
求求你們了
Please.
聽著  這會是一個反覆試驗的情況
Look, this is gonna be a trial-and-error situation.
我們需要排除每一個變量
We have to rule out every variable
來確定出最終可以結束循環的算法
in order to narrow down the correct algorithm that will close the loop.
-好吧  -但這是好多天
- Okay. - Uh, it's days,
甚至好幾周的工作量
maybe weeks of work.
而且如果你說的是真的
And if what you're saying is true,
那麼是沒有辦法記錄我們實驗進度的
there's no way to keep a record of our progress.
我沒有聽明白
I'm not following.
好吧
Okay. Um...
比如說我們要測試很多種變量
Say we test, like, dozens of variables.
在一天結束時  循環就重置了  對嗎
By the end of the day, the loop will reset, right?
所以我們實驗得出結論
So everything we learned gets...
都會被抹掉
...erased.
是沒有辦法可以讓我們跟進進度的
There's no way for us to track our progress
簡單因為我們不會記得
simply because we just don't remember
任何的實驗結論
anything we learned.
所以我們就回到起點了
And we'll be back to square one.
真是太好了
Great.
我完蛋了
I'm screwed.
等下  我明白了
Wait, no, I got it.
你說所有事情都會重置
Okay, you said everything resets
除了你的記憶  對嗎
but your memory, right?
-沒錯  -好吧  那
- Yeah. - All right, well, then...
你只需要變成一個人肉記錄儀
you're just gonna have to be a living record.
等下  你是指記住所有事情嗎
Wait, you mean memorize everything?
-沒錯  -這主意太有才了
- Yeah. - That's genius.
不行  不行  不行
No. No, no, no, no.
這主意一點都不有才  我不是科學家
That's not genius. I'm not a scientist.
而且  我想說  你知道
And hello. I mean, you do realize
有一個殺手在追殺我  對嗎
there's a killer after me, right?
這意味著我需要一遍又一遍地死
That means I'm gonna have to die over and over again
直到你們弄明白如何關掉這個時間循環
until you guys figure out how to close the loop.
我是說  我覺得你可以
I mean, I guess you could
在他們找到你之前自殺
just kill yourself before they find you.
天啊  又一個有才的主意呢
Wow. Another genius idea.
總比被一個帶著嬰兒面具的瘋子追殺好吧
Um, better than being chased by some crazy guy in a baby mask.
那你有更好的主意嗎
I mean, do you have a better idea?
我就知道你會這麼說
I knew you were gonna say that.
錯誤算法
□我只想要  能正常醒來
□ All that I want is to wake up fine
此處BGM  "Hard Times"
歌手  Paramore
□告訴我一切正常  我不會再次死去
□ Tell me that I'm all right, that I ain't gonna die
衣服上寫著FML  意為"去他媽的  這操蛋的生活"
碎樹機  女主名字為Tree翠  也就是樹的意思
別吹了
Ow. Shut up!
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
-我不太確定  -我不太確定
- I wasn't sure if you wanted... - I wasn't sure
你是否想多睡會兒
if you wanted to sleep in or not.
我昨晚幫你疊好了衣服
I folded your clothes last night.
也不確定會不會把衣服折皺
Wasn't sure if that material gets wrinkled.
很好奇  你老是趴在那桌子下面
Anyway, what the hell are you always
翻什麼呢
looking for under that desk?
找我的牙箍
Uh... oh, just... my mouth guard.
因為  我
Yeah, I...
我晚上磨牙
I grind my teeth at night.
解決了一個世界難題
Oh, mystery solved.
□耶  今天是我的生日
□ Yeah, it's my birthday
□我才不打算接電
□ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho...
你沒事吧
You okay?
好的不能再好了
Yep. Never better.
你昨晚醉成那個樣
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
也不知道還記不記得我的名字
You were, uh... you were pretty wasted last night.
我叫卡特
But I'm-I'm Carter.
你確定沒事嗎
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
你臉色死白死白的
You're looking kind of pale.
沒事  我
No, I'm fine. I...
不對  我好像要暈過去了
Actually, I'm probably gonna pass out.
啥
What?
-完了  暈定了  -什麼  別
- Yep. Definitely passing out. - What? No, uh...
你是把那妞上了嗎還是怎
You hit that fine vagine or what?
她這是死了嗎
Is she dead?
-瑞恩  過來幫幫忙  -好的
- Ryan, little help here, man. - Oh, okay.
別怕
Hey, hey. It's okay.
是我而已
It's just me.
你沒事吧  之前可是真的嚇到我了
You okay? You really gave me a scare back there.
嗯  我沒事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
你還是來了
You still came.
當然會來了
Yeah, of course.
為什麼會不來
Why wouldn't I?
我們聯繫了你父母
Oh, we got a hold of your parents.
他們馬上就到
They're on their way.
不行  不能讓他們來  這裡不安全
No. They can't come here. It's not safe.
你說的是什麼意思
What are you talking about?
嚇死我了
Jesus.
你有事嗎
Can I help you?
沒關係  他是我朋友
Oh, it's okay. He's a friend.
對不起  探視時間結束了
Sorry. Visiting hours are over.
好吧  那我走了
All right. Well...
多謝了  卡特
Thanks, Carter.
早點好起來
Yeah. Feel better.
你現在知道我今天為什麼沒去上課了吧
So, I guess now you know why I wasn't in your class today.
對不起  你說什麼
Pardon?
高階生物
Advanced bio.
不好意思
Uh, I'm sorry.
你有選我的課嗎
Are you in my class?
我對你不太臉熟
You don't look familiar.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我記錯了
My mistake.
好吧
Right.
你好  我是巴特勒醫生
Well, I'm Dr. Butler.
見到你很高興
Nice to meet you.
格爾布曼女士  我有點看不明白
Ms. Gelbman, I've been having a hard time
你的病歷
pulling up your medical records.
我知道  看病歷我早該死了
I know. I should be dead.
我的檢查結果不大對勁  是吧
My results, they don't make sense, right?
是的
Yes.
說真的  結果很不好
They're highly alarming, to be honest.
等等
Wait.
幾點了
What time is it?
差不多九點半
Uh, it's almost 9:30.
她快死了
She's about to die.
-誰  -羅麗
- Who? - Lori.
-他要殺了她  -什麼
- He's gonna kill her. - What?
聽我說  你得阻止她去手術室
Listen to me. You need to stop her from going down to the O.R.
不好意思  我不認識你說的這個人
I'm sorry. I don't know who you're talking about.
是嗎  那你老婆應該認識她吧
Oh, really? Well, maybe your wife does.
去啊  快去
Go. Go!
對不住了
Sorry.
羅麗
Lori.
誰放了你
Who set you free?
你是誰
Who are you?
算了
Fine.
一起死得了
I go, you go.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太確定你是否想多睡會兒
I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not.
別吹了
Shut up!
真是受夠了
I am so done with this shit.
用這個歐幾里得矢量乘以
Then you multiplied the Euclidean vector
π的平方根的十七次方
by the square root of pi to the 17th power,
這樣就得到了軸突點0.004
which then gives us an axon point of .004,
然後得到一個為8.2的線性平面矢量
then give us a linear plane vector of 8.2.
沒了
Boom.
厲害
Damn.
如果這些是所有失敗的算法
Well, if these are all the failed algorithms...
那就只剩下一種可能了
Then there's only one possibility left.
牛了個驢糞蛋蛋的  你做到了
Holy shit balls. You did it.
-什麼  成功了嗎  -太好了
- What? It worked? - Yes, yes, yes.
成功了  天啊  居然成功了
It worked? Oh, my God, it worked!
我們成功了
We did it!
激動個什麼勁  我們都不認識她
Why are we so excited? We barely know her.
雖然我也不知道怎麼回事
Honestly, I-I don't know what just happened,
但你寫的那一黑板實在太酷了
but that was impressive.
謝謝
Thanks.
開干吧
Let's do this.
我們再確定一次
Just so we're totally clear,
一個變量會結束這個維度的時間循環
one variant closes the loop in this dimension,
而另一個變量則會把你送回原來的維度
and the other one sends you back to your original dimension
結束那邊的循環
and closes that loop.
到最後決定的時間了
It's final decision time.
留下來  還是回去
Stay here or go back.
我留下
I'm staying here.
不會改的
Final decision.
好  那我們就開始了
Okay. Here we go, then.
往後退兩步
Stand back.
等等
Wait.
怎麼回事
What happened?
矢量出問題了
Oh, the vector's off.
你不是說是對的嗎
But you said this was the right one.
不  公式沒問題  是其他地方的毛病
No, the math was right. Something else is off.
各位  我為了替你們記住這些東西
Guys, I have literally been killing myself
不得不一遍又一遍的自殺
to memorize this shit for you.
我不接受失敗這個結果
Failure's not an option.
怎麼了
What?
硬盤有問題
There's something in hard drive.
肯定是病毒
It must be a virus.
老兄  你是不是又在電腦上看小黃片了
Dude, did you open spam porn again on the computer?
才沒有咧
No.
完了  我得手動把程序輸入一遍了
Great. I have to manually reenter all this code.
要多久
Okay, how long?
六  七個小時吧
Six, seven hours.
瑞恩  你看著我
Ryan, look at me.
我時間不多了
I am on borrowed time here.
聽明白了嗎
Understand?
你必須搞定它
Get it done.
嗯  我現在就在弄了
Uh, yeah, I'm on it.
翠  等等
Tree, wait up.
你確定要這麼幹嗎
Hey. Are you sure about this?
當然確定了
Of course I'm sure.
那兇手怎麼辦
Okay, well, what about the killer?
你說今晚會有人死
I mean, you said people are gonna die tonight.
要是時間循環關閉了  而我們又不幫忙
If you close the loop and we don't help,
他們就死定了
then they're dead for good, aren't they?
我得活著
I have to stay alive.
那個醫院太危險
I can't go back to that hospital.
我不會去的
It's way too risky.
就這樣嗎  你就眼睜睜看著
Okay, so that's it? You're just gonna walk away
無辜的人死掉嗎
and let a bunch of innocent people die?
卡特  每天都有人死
People die every day, Carter.
不能都算在我頭上吧
I can't be responsible for everyone, okay?
雖然聽起來很自私  但理是就這個理
I know how selfish that sounds, but it's true.
不  這聽起來可不是一般的自私
Yeah, no, that sounds incredibly selfish.
你認真的嗎
Are you serious?
這不公平
That's not fair.
你根本不知道這對我有多難
You have no idea how hard this is for me.
我也不想在你跟我媽之間選
I don't want to have to choose between you and my mom,
可我就得選
but I have to.
什麼叫"在我跟你媽之間選"
What do you mean, "choose"?
卡特  另一個維度中
Carter, we're together
我們倆在一起了
in the other dimension.
我每天都像今天一樣
I woke up in your bed every morning,
在你床上醒過來
just like this morning.
我一遍又一遍地重複今天
I did it over and over and over again
最後愛上了你
until I fell in love with you.
可那是另一個維度發生的事情
But that version of us is back there,
我媽活著卻是這個宇宙的事
and my mom is alive here.
所以我做出了選擇
So I've made my decision.
那你錯了怎麼辦
Wh... What if you're wrong?
如果你錯了呢
What if you're wrong?
如果這不是
What if this isn't the life
你該過的生活  怎麼辦
that you're-you're supposed to have?
那又怎樣  那我就活該回到
So, what? I'm just supposed to go back
我媽媽不在了的那個維度嗎
to some dimension where my mom's dead?
我做不到
I can't.
我不想再失去她
I can't lose her again.
可你已經失去她了
You already did.
抹去這個事實的維度對你來說不算真實
And none of this is real if it erases that.
你只是在過著別人的生活
You're just... you're living someone else's life
這個生活不屬於你
that doesn't belong to you.
你經歷過的痛苦和失去
Y-Your pain, th-that loss, that's...
才成就了現在的你
that's what makes you you.
可你現在有機會做的事
But you have the chance to do something
別人卻做夢才能夢到
other people only dream of.
什麼事
What?
你還可以道別
You can say goodbye.
你女朋友叫你了
Your girlfriend's calling you.
我該走了
Better go.
她怎麼了
What's her problem?
她居然不來我們的寢室會
She just ditched our house meeting.
喂
Hello.
你倆聊什麼呢
What were you guys talking about?
沒什麼  就聊聊學校的事
Nothing. We were just... we were going over school stuff.
寶貝  可別忘了
Babe, don't forget,
我的美國文學論文還得靠你呢
I still need help with my American lit paper.
我  我現在真的沒空
I'm... I'm really busy right now.
卡特  你答應過我的
Carter, you promised.
你不幫我的話  這門課我會掛的
I won't pass the class without your help.
好吧  行
All right. Yeah, yeah.
沒問題
That's fine.
你人最好了
You're the best.
另一個女壽星到了
There's the other birthday girl.
親愛的  你這是怎麼了
Sweetie, what's wrong?
我沒事  我
I'm okay. I...
你看起來可不太好
You don't look okay.
我沒事  媽
I'm okay. I... Mom!
你渾身冷得跟冰一樣
You're cold as ice.
要不我們去醫院吧
Maybe we should go to the hospital.
不
No!
不行  不能去醫院
No, we can't go there.
聽著  我是不想嚇到你們
Look, I don't want to freak you guys out,
但是我想要你們盡快離開學校
but I need you to get as far away from campus as possible.
-翠蕾莎  怎麼了  -爸  拜託了
- Theresa, what is going on? - Dad, please.
我保證晚點會給你們解釋的
I promise to explain everything later,
但是我需要你們相信我
but I need you to trust me.
行吧
Okay.
我們走吧
We'll go.
走吧  來
Let's go. Come on.
搞定
Done.
終於完事了
Finally.
你們準備好了嗎
You guys ready?
好  讓我們徹底關閉這個時間循環吧
Okay. Let's close this loop once and for all.
嘿  知道我現在特想吃點什麼嗎
Hey, you know what I'm craving right now?
-什麼  -莫羅貝那家麵包店有的
- What? - One of those giant cinnamon rolls
超大肉桂卷
from that bakery in Morro Bay.
我們去年生日吃過的啊
From our birthday last year?
不記得了嗎  你還吃了兩個呢
You don't remember? You ate two of them.
那不是我
That wasn't me.
說什麼呢  親愛的
What, sweetie?
嘿  姑娘們  天色有些晚了
Hey, girls, it's getting kind of late.
要不我們找個地方
What do you say we find someplace,
住一晚吧
turn in for the night?
行  聽起來不錯
Okay, sounds good.
我想大家都很累了
I think we're all pretty pooped.
貝菲爾德供電站
羅麗
Lori!
靠
Shit.
她被抓了  她被抓了
He got her, he got her!
不  別開槍  別開槍
No, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
你會打到凱的
You might hit Kay.
信息大意  瑞恩: 系統準備好了  希望萬事大吉
姑娘們  我去拿點冰
Hey, girls, I'm gonna go get some ice.
馬上回來
I'll be right back.
好了
Okay.
實話告訴我
Just tell me one thing.
你懷孕了嗎
Are you pregnant?
什麼
What?
沒有  媽媽  我
No. Mom, I...
好吧  抱歉  但我必須得問
Okay, sorry. I just had to ask.
不是這樣的
It's not like that.
但還是和男生有關  對吧
But it's a boy, isn't it?
不是
No.
算是吧
Yes.
我也不知道  事情有點複雜
I don't know. It's complicated.
相信我
Trust me.
多複雜我也能理解
I can do complicated.
是怎麼回事
What is it?
你有沒有想過如果沒有和爸爸在一起的話
Have you ever wondered what your life would have been like
你會有怎樣的生活
if you couldn't be with Dad?
什麼  沒想過
What? No.
但如果你必須做出選擇呢
But what if you had to choose?
就是  如果跟他在一起
You know, what if... what if being with him meant
你就會失去和你一個非常親密的人
that you would lose someone that you were really close to,
而且再也見不到那個人
that you would never get to see that person ever again?
那你會怎麼做
What would you do?
我們都有要做出艱難選擇的時候  翠
Well, we all have to make hard choices, Tree.
這就是生活
That's life.
有時候  過去會牽引我們往一個方向走
And sometimes the past is pulling us in one direction
而未來卻在另一個方向召喚我們
and the future is calling us somewhere new.
但是毫無疑問  如果必須選擇
But, of course, if I had to choose,
我會選你爸爸
I'd pick Daddy.
我是說  沒有他也就不會有你  對吧
I mean, without him, I wouldn't have you, right?
但你怎麼知道他就是命中注定的那一個呢
But how did you know that he was the one?
我並不知道
I didn't.
我只是碰碰運氣
I took a chance.
遵從自己的心意
I followed my heart.
這就是愛  翠
That's kind of how love works, Tree.
也就是放手一搏
It's a leap of faith.
在貝菲爾德大學醫院
...Bayfield University Hospital,
慘案仍在發生
where a terrible tragedy continues to unfold.
相關信息陸續公開
Details are still coming in,
截至目前已確認三名受害者
but so far, we can confirm three victims.
一名護士和一名警察被害
A nurse and a police officer.
第三名受害者是個學生
The third victim, a student,
在試圖制服嫌疑犯時不幸遇害
was killed while attempting to subdue the suspect.
以上是前線報道  主持人
Back to you, Dan.
不
No.
怎麼了
What's wrong?
快點電話  瑞恩  快接
Come on, Ryan. Come on.
薩瑪  能幫忙
Hey, Samar, can you
-查一下22 97 39嗎  -好的
- check 22-97-39 right there? - Uh, yeah.
那邊
Over there.
等等  矢量需要調整一下
No, the vector needs to be adjusted.
喲  我是瑞恩  聽到嗶聲後請留言
Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a message at the beep...!
瑞恩  不要關閉時間循環
Ryan, don't close the loop.
-你不能  -抱歉
- You can't... - I'm sorry.
-語音信箱已滿  -靠
- This voice mailbox is... - Shit!
翠  發生什麼事了
Tree, what is going on?
我不能讓他關閉循環
I can't let him close it.
我說不准這冰是怎麼了
You know, I'm not sure about this ice.
聞起來像尿一樣
It kind of smells like pee.
翠
Tree?
翠  你去哪裡
Tree! Where are you going?
翠
Tree!
快接電話
Come on.
快接電話  接電話  快接電話
Come on, come on! Pick up your phone!
-喲  我是瑞恩 聽到  -操
- Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a... - Shit!
開始吧
Here we go.
在哪裡  快點  快點
Where is it? Come on, come on, come on. Please.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太確定你是否想多睡會兒
I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not.
那是我最後一次為你去死
That is the last time I'm dying for you.
什麼
What?
還要多久時間
How much longer is it gonna take?
多虧你驚人的記憶力  應該用不了多久
Thanks to your crazy memory, it shouldn't take long at all.
幾分鐘後就可以讓西西裝置準備就緒
I can have Sissy ready to go in just a few minutes.
我還需要一點點時間
I need a little more time.
我還有些事要做
There's something I need to do.
翠
Tree.
你確定要回去嗎
You sure you want to go back?
總不能一輩子活在過去裡
Can't spend my life living in the past.
要有點信心放手一搏
Got to take a leap of faith.
可算回來了
She finally rolls in.
羅麗  你好
Lori, hi.
昨晚很忙吧
Big night?
差不多吧
You could say that.
聽著  羅麗  我
Um, look, Lori, I...
見到你很開心
It's good to see you.
什
Wha...?
我也很開心能見到你  翠
It's good to see you, too, Tree.
他不值得
He's not worth it.
我是說  相信我
I mean, trust me.
我也曾和一個已婚男人有一腿
I've been involved with a married guy.
也清楚以雙重身份生活是什麼滋味
I know what it's like living a double life.
總是覺得自己很差勁
Always feeling like shit about yourself.
但是浪子回頭金不換
But it's never too late to change.
曾經有人和我說
Someone once told me that
"每一天都是一個讓自己更優秀的機會"
"every day is a chance to be someone better."
或許今天就是你變得更優秀的日子
Maybe this is your day.
好吧
Okay.
謝謝你
Thank you.
照顧好自己
Take care of yourself.
翠
Tree.
嘿
Hey.
那個  丹妮爾  我很難過
Um... look, Danielle, I feel really bad.
之前一直誤會你
I've totally been misjudging you,
都是我的錯
and it's completely on me.
-我很抱歉  我想把  -贊啊
- I am so sorry that I've, like, made this... - Nice.
三人行
Three-way.
他開玩笑呢
He's kidding.
不  我沒開玩笑
No, I'm-I'm not.
尼克的  呃  花灑壞了
Nick's, um, shower was broken,
所以我讓他借用我的
so I said he could use mine.
對吧  尼克
Right, Nick?
我的花灑好著呢
My shower's fine.
好吧  那個  當我沒說
Right. Um, you know what? Never mind.
抱歉打擾你們了
Sorry for interrupting.
拜拜
Bye-ee.
打我幹嘛
What was that for?
因為你蠢得跟石頭一樣
For being dumb as a rock. That's what.
哦  是嗎  石頭怎麼會蠢
Oh, really? How can a rock be dumb?
他們連腦子都沒有
They don't even have brains.
另一個女壽星到了
There's the other birthday girl.
-你好啊  親愛的  -你好  老爸
-Hi, sweetie. - Hey, Dad.
能讓我和媽媽單獨聊兩句嗎
Um, do you mind if I talk to Mom alone for a minute?
就是些女孩間的私房話
Just some girl talk.
當然可以了
Oh. Well, sure.
那我去打幾個工作電話
I-I can go run some work calls.
好的  謝謝
Okay, thanks.
一切都還好嗎
Is everything okay?
嗯  都很好
Yeah. It's fine.
一切都好
Everything's fine.
糟糕  我要怎麼開口
Oh, shit, how do I do this?
說什麼  親愛的  怎麼了
Do what, sweetie? What's wrong?
媽媽
Mom...
我真想讓你知道我有多愛你
I really want you to know how much I love you.
我也好愛你  親愛的
I love you, too, sweetie.
不是的  媽媽  我是認真的
No, Mom, I'm serious.
人們總是說 我愛你
You know, people say "I love you"
但是
all the time, but...
只有在你無法再次當面說出這句話的時候
it's not until you can't say it to that person's face anymore
才會發現自己有多深愛著對方
that you really realize how much you mean it.
你如此完美又如此漂亮
You are so beautiful and so amazing.
我只希望有一天
And I just hope I can become
我能有你一半的好
half of the woman that you are one day.
你是在說笑嗎
Are you kidding?
因為有了你  我才變成了現在的自己
I'm the woman I am because I had you.
這話我還從沒對其他人說過
You know, I never really told anyone this before,
當我懷上你的時候  我嚇得手足無措
but when I was pregnant with you, I was scared shitless.
不
No.
但當我抱著你的時候
But then, the moment I held you,
我內心的某些部分就立刻改變了
something inside of me changed instantly.
最偉大的愛就是這樣
The best kind of love does that.
它會改變你
It changes you.
使你成為一個更好的人
It makes you a better person.
天啊  我太笨了
Oh, God, I'm so stupid.
我真的以為我可以擁有一切  但我不能
I really thought I could have it all, but I can't.
親愛的  沒人可以擁有一切
Oh, honey, nobody can.
但你猜怎麼著
But guess what.
這沒關係
That's okay.
你會得到你需要的
You'll get what you need.
我希望如此
I hope so.
過來吧
Aw. Come here.
我壓著你了嗎
Am I crushing you?
沒有
Nope.
你永遠是我的小女兒
You're always gonna be my little girl.
□祝你生日快樂
□ Happy birthday to you
□祝翠和媽媽生日快樂
□ Happy birthday, Tree and Mom
□祝你生日快樂
□ Happy birthday to you.
許個願吧
Make a wish.
準備好了嗎
You ready?
等等
Wait.
聽我說
Look...
我知道這可能非常令人困惑
I know this is probably pretty confusing.
我是說  你們認識我才幾個小時
I mean, you guys have only known me for a couple hours,
但我已經認識你們幾個星期了
but I've known you for weeks.
你們都很努力地
You've all worked really, really hard
試圖幫我送回家
to try to send me home.
所以謝謝你們
So thank you.
陪審團仍在討論你是否完全瘋了
Well, jury's still out on whether you're totally nuts,
但很高興我們能幫上忙
But I glad we could help.
好了  瑞恩  啟動吧
Okay, Ryan, light her up.
所以  在另一個維度  我們
S-So, in this other dimension, do we...
我們認識嗎
do we know each other?
你可以這麼說
You could say that.
17秒
17 seconds.
16 15  14
sixteen, fifteen, fourteen...
我是怎麼跟你說的  不要打開那個東西
What did I tell you about turning that thing on?
等一下  這還不應該發生
Uh-oh. Wait. This isn't supposed to happen yet.
你應該明天才來
You're not supposed to come until tomorrow.
現在把那東西關掉
Turn that thing off now.
不  不要
No, don't!
不  不  不
No, no, no, no! No, no!
不  求你了  你不能這樣做
No, wait, please. You can't do this.
-你是誰  -我是這裡的學生
- And who are you? - I am a student here.
好吧  如果你繼續是這樣的態度
Oh, well, keep this little attitude up,
你很快就不是了
and we'll change that.
把那東西拿出去
Get that thing out of here.
-不  請不要  -小心點  猛男
- No, please d-don't. - Hey, watch it, beefcake.
別這樣  我們花了18個月在它身上
Don't. Don't. We spent 18 months on that thing.
求你了  求你了  別這樣
Please, please don't. Please.
別這麼粗暴
Well, don't manhandle her.
拿
Take...
你要把她帶去哪兒
Well, where are you taking her?
我要把它鎖在我的辦公室裡
My office, where it will remain under lock and key.
好吧  這是個挫折  我明白
Look, okay, it's a setback. I get it.
但我們可以重新過一遍今天  再試一次
Right, but we just reset the day and try again.
不  你不明白
No. You don't understand.
每次回來我都越來越虛弱
I keep getting weaker every time I come back.
我不知道我還有多少機會
I don't know how many chances I have left.
據我所知  這可能就是最後一次機會了
For all I know, this could be it.
如果我這一次死了  我也不能復活了
If I die again, I could stay dead.
-這可是個大問題  -操蛋
- Hmm, that's a problem. - Oh shit.
除非
Unless...
除非我們把它偷回來
Unless we steal it back.
偷回來嗎
Steal it?
我是說  你知道的
Well, I mean, you know,
嚴格說  這甚至都不算偷竊  不是嗎
it's not even technically stealing, is it?
這是你們的東西
It's your property.
夥計們  我可不知道
Whoa, whoa, guys, I don't know about this.
如果我們被抓了  我被開除了
Like, if we get caught and I get expelled,
我父母可是要把我吊在麻袋邊往死裡打的
my parents are gonna hang me by the nut sack.
我加入他
I'm with him.
當然不是說一起當麻袋
Except for the "nut sack" part, obviously.
你在開玩笑吧
Are you kidding me? Are...
不  我很抱歉在這裡我
No. I'm sorry to throw a bag of dog shit
要倒戈相向了  但我
on your front porch here, but I...
這全都怪你們
This is all on you guys.
你們弄了這個爛攤子
You created this mess,
所以你們有義務幫助她擺脫困境
so you're obligated to help her out of it.
另外  如果她今晚又死了
Besides, if she dies again tonight,
你們都脫不了關係
that's blood on your hands.
這可有點戲劇性
That's a little dramatic.
他說的對
He's right.
這是我們的錯
This is our fault.
所以我們得糾正它
So we fix it.
科學家就得這麼做
That's what scientists do.
科學家專門解決問題
We solve the problem.
布洛森院長的辦公室就在這幢樓裡
So, Dean Bronson's office is in this building here,
回到實驗室最快的就是這條路
and the fastest route back to the lab is this path here.
看看這個  夥計們  布洛森院長
And check this out, guys. Dean Bronson spends
每天晚上都在教員休息室裡織毛衣
every evening knitting in the faculty lounge over here.
等等  什麼  織毛衣嗎
Wait, what? He knits?
我以為他在那裡抽煙
I think he used to smoke,
然後他的妻子讓他戒煙  而且
and then his wife made him quit, and, uh...
順便說一句  他妻子太火辣了
Oh, by the way, shockingly hot.
薩瑪
Samar?
我們能
Could we do the-the thing we're...
專注一點嗎
we're doing right now?
好吧  對不起  沒問題
Right. Sorry. Um, okay.
所以  我們需要拿到他辦公室的鑰匙
So, we need to get the keys to his office,
然後溜到招生處  闖進院長辦公室
sneak over to admissions, break into the dean's office,
拿到西西裝置  把她帶回實驗室
grab Sissy, wheel her back to the lab
還不能讓安保人員看到我們
without anyone from security seeing us,
還需要把布洛森院長的鑰匙還給他
get Dean Bronson's keys back to him
但不能讓他知道鑰匙被偷了
without him ever knowing they were gone,
給西西裝置通電  運行程序
power up Sissy, run diagnostics,
打開開關  砰的一聲  翠就回去了
flip the switch, and bam... Tree's back
回到她來的那個古怪的維度
in whatever wack-ass dimension she came from,
我們  我們就挽救了這該死的一天
and we... well, we just saved the damn day.
可以
Okay.
聽起來棒極了
Sounds awesome.
-我們怎麼做到這個計劃  -我不知道
- How do we do that? - I don't know.
-你當然不知道  -好吧  好吧
- Of course. - Okay, well,
我們顯然需要轉移院長的注意力
we obviously need a diversion.
所以我們得想個辦法分散他的注意力
So we just got to find a way to distract Dean Bronson.
她選的鈴聲  好嗎  我
Uh, she picked the ringtone, all right? I...
嘿  寶貝
Hey, babe.
是的  你還好嗎
Yeah, uh, you okay?
-我有個主意  -你說
- I-I have an idea. - Okay.
如果我們從這邊過去呢
What if we actually go through...
我在和瑞恩還有他們還有
With Ryan and them and...
-丹妮爾  你好啊  -她不是
- Danielle, hi. - She's not...
我們要請你幫個小忙
So, we have a little favor to ask.
我也覺得可疑
I feel suspect at best.
讓我們把臉放過去
Let's just put our face in.
嘿  寶貝
Hey, baby.
好吧  對不起
Oh. Okay, sorry.
顯然  她有點緊張
Clearly, she's a little on edge.
-說的對  -給她一些喘息的空間
- That's right. - Give her some room to breathe...
瞎說
Preach.
需要我幫助你嗎
Can I help you?
(西語)抱歉
Oh, perdon.
我似乎  呃  迷路了
I appear to be, uh, very lost.
我是羅傑·布洛森  學校的院長
Roger Bronson. I'm the dean of the school.
(法語)哦  你好
Oh, bonjour.
我的名字是  呃  愛美莉·勒·皮尤
My name is, uh, Amelie Le Pew.
你一定是交換生吧
Oh. You must be with the exchange program.
(法語)啊  是的
Ah, oui, oui.
先生  我能摸摸你的臉嗎
Monsieur, may I know your face?
你說什麼
I'm sorry?
-好吧  -我的天吶
- My. Oh, my. - Oh, my!
容貌真有特色
What strong features.
謝謝您
Thank you.
你一定是法國人
You must be French.
你的手聞起來像奶酪
Your hand smells like cheese.
我不吃奶酪
I don't eat cheese.
我有  呃
Ah, I am, uh...
乳糖不耐症
...uh, lactose intolerant.
(法語)哦  真遺憾
Oh, quelle dommage.
你想去哪裡
Uh, uh... uh, where are you trying to get to?
(法語)呃  咖啡館
Uh, le cafe.
你一定是指餐廳吧
Oh, you must mean the cafeteria.
我很樂意給你指路  走這邊  我可以
I'm happy to show you. Here, here. I can... Uh, whoa!
別動  你會絆倒的
Oh, oh! Oh, don't move! You'll trip.
哦  彈珠
Oh, marbles.
彈珠  到處都是彈珠
Marbles! Marbles everywhere.
快走
Go, go, go, go.
哦  天吶
Oh, boy.
小心點
Careful.
走的很快啊
Pretty quick there.
等一下好嗎  別動  好嗎
Hold on, now. Just stay put, okay?
我只需要  呃  拿上我的鑰匙
I just need to, uh, grab my keys.
哦  別碰掛毯
Oh! Not the tapestry.
哦  天哪
Oh, geez.
哦  上帝啊  哦  哦  不
Oh. Oh, Lord. Oh, oh, oh! Oh, no!
哦  不  太黑了
Oh, no. It's so dark.
向燈光方向移動
Move toward the light.
哦  對不起  說錯話了
Oh, sorry, that was insensitive.
來吧
Come on.
-快點  快點  -我在努力
- Come on, come on, come on. - I'm trying.
別滾動了  好嗎
Stop rolling. Okay.
你是在幫倒忙  滾反了
You're not helping. The other way.
-西西裝置  -快帶走
- Sissy. - Go, go.
走  快走
Go around, go around.
這邊
This way.
薩瑪  薩瑪
Samar. Samar.
好的  好了
Okay, okay.
好了  起來  起來
Here we go. Up. Up.
哦  天哪
Oh, God.
這是你的枴杖
Here's your cane.
你真的不能再到處亂跑了
You really must stop wandering around.
-(西語)謝謝  -好了  走吧
- Gracias. - Okay. Okay. Shall we?
忘記帶鑰匙了
Ah, forgot my keys.
-天吶  -(法語)哦不  我的上帝
- Oh, God! - Oh, no, mon Dieu.
天吶
God!
我流了好多血
Oh, that's a lot of blood.
天吶  小心點用你的枴杖
Jesus, be careful with that thing.
-我很抱歉  -我的天啊
- I am so sorry. - Oh, my God.
我覺得使用枴杖對你來說不是個好主意
Oh, I don't think the cane is a good idea for you.
你需要一隻導盲犬
You need a Seeing Eye dog.
將軍咯
Checkmate.
情況如何了
Hey. How's it going?
正在努力
We're on it.
老兄  還剩下不到三個小時了
Guys, we've got less than three hours
趕緊讓它啟動啊
to make this happen.
我不騙你  馬上就完事了
Not gonna lie... it's gonna be close.
媽的
Shit.
如果不阻止兇手的話  羅麗會死的
If I don't stop the killer, Lori's gonna die.
你守在這裡
Stay here.
什麼  你要幹什麼
What? Why?
別管  只要保證你會守在這裡就行
Just promise me you'll stay here.
能借用一下嗎
Can I borrow this?
呃  當然  隨便
Uh, y-yeah, sure.
好的
Okay.
等等  你要去哪裡
W-Wait, where are you going?
翠
Tree!
抱歉  來的挺不是時候的
Sorry, bad timing.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
行吧  允許你把它收起來
Okay, you can put it away.
快點的  塞回去
Come on, put it away.
現在把身子慢慢的轉過來
Okay, now slowly turn around.
你這是在犯下大錯
This is a really bad idea.
醫院裡現有個殺人狂魔出沒
There's a killer on the loose here.
快去找點援手
Go get help.
-你說什麼  -快走
- What? - Go!
這個女的有槍  這女的有槍啊
She's got a gun! She's got a gun!
羅麗  讓開
Lori, move.
-什麼鬼  -快點  我們該走了
- What? - Come on, we've got to move.
-到底怎麼回事  -路上解釋  快走
- What's happening? - I'll explain later. Move!
這什麼情況
What is this?
你根本不瞎
You're not blind.
我要弄死他們
I'm gonna kill them.
我一定要弄死他們
I'm going to kill them!
他朝你們去了
He's onto us.
寶貝  能幫忙把我太陽眼鏡拿回來了嗎
Babe, can you also get my sunglasses back?
還沒戴熱乎呢
I just got those.
-使勁啊使勁  快點  -知道
- Okay, okay, come on. - Yes.
給我弄開
Get it open now.
快點  快點
Get it, get it.
給我撞啊
Bash it in.
-別讓他們進來  -我們在努力了
- Keep 'em out. -We're trying!
趕緊給我弄開
Get it open now!
要是被開除了  父母會和我斷絕關係的
Oh, my God. If I get expelled, my parents are gonna disown me.
翠  能行行好告訴我到底怎麼回事嗎
Tree, will you please tell me what's going on?
一開始我只是單純的以為他想殺我
At first, I thought he was trying to kill me,
-但沒想到目標其實是你  -誰的目標
- but it's you he's after. - Who?
格瑞格裡  到此為止了
It's over, Gregory.
什麼  為什麼會是你
What? Why?
他老婆發現了你跟他搞外遇
His wife found out about your affair.
所以他就照抄了你之前的方法
So he stole a page from your old playbook.
他先把湯布斯放了  這樣大家就會
He set Tombs free, knowing that everyone
認為他才是罪魁禍首
would think that he killed you.
再把你弄死  劈腿的事就無人知曉了
And the secret of your affair would die with you.
精彩
Bravo.
真是精彩至極啊
Well done, indeed.
一日偷吃  終身為賊
Once a douchebag, always a douchebag.
不好意思  您是哪根蔥
I'm sorry, do I know you?
別動  你個禽獸
Stay back, asshole.
把吃奶的勁也給我用上
Put your back into it!
再使使勁啊
Try harder.
你倆這點小勁對得起身上的肉嗎
You guys got to get back into the gym, man.
瑞恩  我們快撐不住了
Ryan, we can't hold it much longer.
快點  快點啊
Come on, come on.
聽到了嗎
You hear that?
馬上你就得把牢底坐穿了
You're gonna rot in prison.
我可不這麼想哦
I don't think so.
你的推理漏掉了那麼一個細節
You see, there's one little detail
百密的這一疏會讓你滿盤皆輸
you failed to realize in all this.
真的嗎  我漏掉了什麼呢
Oh, really? What's that?
我啊
Me.
羅麗
Lori!
你難不成還真以為
You really think I was gonna let
我會乖乖等著這個婊子毀掉我的生活嗎
a little whore like that ruin my life?
格瑞格裡  利索點
Gregory, kill her.
超度的重任就交給你了
Would you like to do the honors?
榮幸之至
Don't mind if I do.
哦  等等  我差點忘了
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
我想和你離婚了
I want a divorce.
好吧  說到哪裡了
Now, where were we?
嘿
Hey!
真可悲  你是想用這個螺絲刀戳死我嗎
Aw, look who brought a screwdriver to a gunfight.
等會
Wait.
我還需要告訴你一個事
I have something I need to tell you.
什麼事
What?
你死定了
You're screwed.
你個賤人  快把它關掉
Turn it off, you bitch.
不不不  等  等等
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, wait. Wait!
準備好了嗎  來吧
Ready? Come on.
你能行的  我撐著你
There you go. I got you.
沒事的
I got you.
好勒  大功告成
All right. Yep.
我的天啊  你還好吧
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
這地方挨個槍子都跟破了個皮似的
I guess this is a pretty good place to get shot, huh?
我要把你抱起來了  好嗎
I'll lift you up now, all right?
你會沒事的  你很堅強
You're gonna be okay. You're good.
慢一點  慢一點
It's okay, it's okay.
你會好起來的
You're okay.
羅麗  我
Lori, I...
我真心感到抱歉
I'm so sorry.
道什麼歉呢
For what?
你可是我的救命恩人啊
You just saved my life.
我只是
I just...
我希望事情原本可以有所不同
I wish things could have been different.
打擾一下  我們得開始轉移了
I'm sorry, but we need to move her.
堅持住啊
Hang in there, hon.
嘿
Hey.
你沒事吧
Hey. You okay?
呃  沒有
Uh, yeah.
沒事  我沒事  我只是
Yeah, I'm fine. I...
我記得告訴過你不要來醫院
I thought I told you to stay put.
啊哈  確實
Yeah, well...
抱歉  忍不住就來了
sorry, couldn't help myself.
看來到時候了
I think it's time.
我希望你知道  我回來只是為了一件事
I hope you realize I'm only going back for one reason.
我的媽啊
Oh, man.
我的飲料啊
My Yoo-hoo.
丹妮爾
Danielle?
咋回事啊
Who?
你好啊
Hi.
臥槽等等  我好像拉褲子了
Oh, my God. I think I just shit my pants.
後有彩蛋  空降坐標01:33:06
片尾曲  "Stayin' Alive"
歌手  Bee Gees
□活著  就是圖個痛快
□ Ah, ah, ah, ah Stayin' alive... ooh... yeah
□從哥的腳步中就看得出來
□ Whoo, well, you can tell by the way I use my walk
□哥是大眾情人  不必多說
□ I'm a woman, no time to talk
□音樂很吵 女孩很躁
□ Music loud and women warm, I've been kicked around
□打從娘胎裡出來哥就在四處遊蕩
□ Since I was born
□現在氣氛剛剛好
□ And now it's all right, it's okay
□你可以換個角度去思考
□ And you may look the other way
□給我使勁的思考
□ We can try to understand Uh-huh, uh-huh
□紐約時報都對咱干了啥好事
□ The New York Times' effect on man
□無論你是摳腳大漢  還是貴為人母
□ Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother
□你都實實在在地活著  痛快地活著
□ You're stayin' alive, stayin' alive
□城市在發展  人們在律動
□ Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin'
□我們都實實在在地活著  痛快活著
□ And we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive
活著 就要享受生活
□ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive, stayin' alive
活著  就是圖個痛快
□ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive...
□現如今  哥在人海中浮浮沉沉
□ Well, now, I get low and I get high
□雖高不成低不就  但哥真的很努力
□ And if I can't get either, I really try
□哥可是鞋上長翅膀的男人
□ Got the wings of heaven on my shoes
□騷起舞來  誰與爭鋒
□ I'm dancin' and I just can't lose
□現在氣氛剛剛好
□ And now it's all right, it's okay
□哥會笑著看到明天的太陽
□ I'll live to see another day
□給我使勁的琢磨
□ We can try to understand
□紐約時報都對咱干了啥好事
□ The New York Times' effect on man
□無論你是摳腳大漢  還是貴為人母
□ Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother
□你都實實在在地活著  痛快地活著
□ You're stayin' alive, stayin' alive
□城市在發展  人們在律動
□ Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin'
□我們都實實在在地活著  痛快活著
□ And we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive
□活著  就要享受生活
□ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive, stayin' alive
□活著  就得圖個痛快
□ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive...
□我只想痛痛快快地活著
□ I'm stayin' alive
□生活將去向何方  誰懂哥的寂寞
□ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me
□有誰懂哥的寂寞
□ Somebody help me, yeah
□我只想痛快地活著
□ I'm stayin' alive
□生活將去向何方 誰懂哥的寂寞
□ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me. Yeah
□有誰能懂哥的寂寞
□ Somebody help me, yeah
□生活將去向何方  誰懂哥深沉的寂寞
□ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me, yeah.
根本沒道理啊
Just doesn't make any sense.
當然有道理啊
Yes, it does.
這就像個彈弓似的
It acted like a slingshot.
當她跳回這個維度時
When she jumped back into this dimension,
向心力產生的真空會使時間循環閉合
the vacuum created by the centripetal force closed the loop.
誰這麼造孽把這麼完好的小油條扔地上了
Who throws away a perfectly good churro?
噢你別  別吃啊
Oh, no, don't.
啊哦  看上去有點不妙
Uh-oh. This looks bad.
你是瑞恩 凡嗎
Ryan Phan?
呃  好像是我吧
Uh, maybe.
我是艾薩克·帕克博士  代表DARPA
I'm Dr. Isaac Parker. I'm here on behalf of DARPA.
DARPA  美國國防高級研究計劃局
Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency
如果你能配合我們進行一些調查
We'd appreciate it if you'd come with us
我們將不勝感激
to answer some questions.
你們所有人
All of you.
我們惹了什麼麻煩嗎
Are we in trouble?
好了  這邊請
Please, right this way.
卡利巴托博士請到人工智能區
Dr. Kalibato to Robotics.
臥了個大槽
Holy shit.
西西裝置
Sissy.
希望你們不介意我們徵用了她
Hope you don't mind us borrowing her.
你們在這裡的所作所為令人歎為觀止
What you've created here is truly remarkable.
一邊玩去吧  布洛森院長
Suck it, Dean Bronson.
我們在研究這個裝置時
We've been having some difficulties
遇到了一些困難
understanding how the device operates.
我覺得你們能幫上忙
We figured you could help.
這個有很多不同的算法
There's so many different algorithms.
很難找到合適的方法能讓它穩定發揮作用
It'll be tough to find the right one to make it work.
我也許能幫上忙哦
I might be able to help with that.
很好
Great.
所以  我們只缺一個測試對象了
So, we just need to find a test subject.
等等  你們是想把人困在時間循環裡嗎
Wait, you... you want to trap somebody in a time loop?
這太扯淡了
That's messed up.
當然除非有人活該
Unless they deserve it.
我想到了個完美的候選人
I think I have the perfect recruit.